<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Textsmate</title>
    <link>https://www.textsmate.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Textsmate</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 22:12:34 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.textsmate.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Elon Musk Child Name Is X Æ A-12</title>
      <link>https://www.textsmate.com/2020/elon-musk-daughter-name/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 22:12:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.textsmate.com/2020/elon-musk-daughter-name/</guid>
      <description>Maybe Elon Musk and Grimes&amp;rsquo; baby name will win for &amp;lsquo;the most controversial baby name.&amp;rsquo;
For the first their child&amp;rsquo;s name is pronounced &amp;ldquo;X Ash Archangel&amp;rdquo;
Gwyneth Paltrow, whose daughter name maybe the second, her daughter name is Apple.
Grimes explained that they chosed a name sounds like it could be a Star Warsdroid.
X means &amp;ldquo;the unkown variable&amp;rdquo;
Æ is her &amp;ldquo;elven spelling&amp;rdquo; of &amp;ldquo;ai&amp;rdquo;, In Chinese, ai means Love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quotes From Richard Feynman</title>
      <link>https://www.textsmate.com/2020/richard-feynman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 May 2020 09:56:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.textsmate.com/2020/richard-feynman/</guid>
      <description>The quotes is from https://twitter.com/ProfFeynman
  It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter how beautiful your theory is, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter how smart you are. If it doesn&amp;rsquo;t agree with experiment, it&amp;rsquo;s wrong. In that simple statement is the key to science.
  Stupidity is knowing the truth, seeing the truth but still believing the lies.
  Failure is an incredible learning experience. It teaches you humility. It teaches you to work harder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quotes For Lovely Mothers</title>
      <link>https://www.textsmate.com/2020/words-for-mothers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 14:22:57 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.textsmate.com/2020/words-for-mothers/</guid>
      <description>I heard that God couldn&amp;rsquo;t be everywhere, so he created Mom.
  I met my mother when she was only 23 years old, and I imagine that the first time my mother met me must have been the most beautiful time of her life. It&amp;rsquo;s just that at the time I must have been crying constantly, so I forgot to look at my mom at her best.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Letters From This Site Will Self Destruct</title>
      <link>https://www.textsmate.com/2020/this-site-will-self-destruct/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 08:06:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.textsmate.com/2020/this-site-will-self-destruct/</guid>
      <description>The website is https://www.thiswebsitewillselfdestruct.com/
You can post a letter to the website which will display your letter on the website.
We collect some meaningful letter for you.
 Dear Website,I just finished a 15 hour shift at the hospital. I’m a doctor in Australia. We’re so lucky here, and I feel awful about how supportive our community is for us in a situation frankly overstated in our part of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Words as Your Bio in Twitter and Instagram</title>
      <link>https://www.textsmate.com/2020/words-as-your-bio-in-twitter-and-instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 19:16:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.textsmate.com/2020/words-as-your-bio-in-twitter-and-instagram/</guid>
      <description>I live on a lonely little monster planet. Sober people are the most ridiculous. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait for your blatant preference after all. It&amp;rsquo;s better to be missed than to be missed You&amp;rsquo;re my star and I&amp;rsquo;m trillions of years away. I&amp;rsquo;m sunny and funny, dark and loving. Miss you, but won&amp;rsquo;t look for you. when he acts more than he swears, you meet the right man. All the tenderness from a coarse life is just for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kobe Bryant Quotes Keep Us Fighting</title>
      <link>https://www.textsmate.com/2020/mamba-forever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 18:41:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.textsmate.com/2020/mamba-forever/</guid>
      <description>Mamba will remain in our heart forever
 There are some words from Kobe Bryant  Rest at the end, not in the middle.
It’s the one thing you can control. You are responsible for how people remember you—or don’t. So don’t take it lightly.
The topic of leadership is a touchy one. A lot of leaders fail because they don’t have the bravery to touch that nerve or strike that chord.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>