<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Textsmate</title>
    <link>https://www.textsmate.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Textsmate</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 08:06:07 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.textsmate.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Letters From This Site Will Self Destruct</title>
      <link>https://www.textsmate.com/2020/this-site-will-self-destruct/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 08:06:07 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.textsmate.com/2020/this-site-will-self-destruct/</guid>
      <description>The website is https://www.thiswebsitewillselfdestruct.com/
You can post a letter to the website which will display your letter on the website.
We collect some meaningful letter for you.
 Dear Website,I just finished a 15 hour shift at the hospital. I’m a doctor in Australia. We’re so lucky here, and I feel awful about how supportive our community is for us in a situation frankly overstated in our part of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Words as Your Bio in Twitter and Instagram</title>
      <link>https://www.textsmate.com/2020/words-as-your-bio-in-twitter-and-instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 19:16:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.textsmate.com/2020/words-as-your-bio-in-twitter-and-instagram/</guid>
      <description>I live on a lonely little monster planet. Sober people are the most ridiculous. I can&amp;rsquo;t wait for your blatant preference after all. It&amp;rsquo;s better to be missed than to be missed You&amp;rsquo;re my star and I&amp;rsquo;m trillions of years away. I&amp;rsquo;m sunny and funny, dark and loving. Miss you, but won&amp;rsquo;t look for you. when he acts more than he swears, you meet the right man. All the tenderness from a coarse life is just for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kobe Bryant Quotes Keep Us Fighting</title>
      <link>https://www.textsmate.com/2020/mamba-forever/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 18:41:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.textsmate.com/2020/mamba-forever/</guid>
      <description>Mamba will remain in our heart forever
 There are some words from Kobe Bryant  Rest at the end, not in the middle.
It’s the one thing you can control. You are responsible for how people remember you—or don’t. So don’t take it lightly.
The topic of leadership is a touchy one. A lot of leaders fail because they don’t have the bravery to touch that nerve or strike that chord.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>